<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>artist on Ouirich Bounthavy</title>
    <link>https://ouirich.github.io/tags/artist/</link>
    <description>Recent content in artist on Ouirich Bounthavy</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 22:22:22 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ouirich.github.io/tags/artist/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Leo</title>
      <link>https://ouirich.github.io/filmography/leo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 22:22:22 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ouirich.github.io/filmography/leo/</guid>
      <description>Coming back to Animal Logic after five years as a senior lighting artist. The studio developped their own lighting software for their USD pipeline. But thanks to my previous experience, it was fairly easy to pick it up. Mostly because the logic behind it, was still the same.
We don&amp;rsquo;t always work on the most exciting shots on a production. As I started, another artist left. So I ended up picking up their shots to complete them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spidey and his Amazing Friends</title>
      <link>https://ouirich.github.io/filmography/spideyamagingfriends/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 21:43:25 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ouirich.github.io/filmography/spideyamagingfriends/</guid>
      <description>I worked on 6 shorts and 10 episodes of the first season. Each episode was 11 minutes long and usually had between 4 or 5 keyshots. Most of the time I was in charge of 2 or 3 that had effects. My role was to setup keyshots in lighting and compositing beforehand. I would then work with my team on the rest of the episode.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LEGO Marvel Avengers: Climate Conundrum</title>
      <link>https://ouirich.github.io/filmography/lma/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2020 14:34:15 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ouirich.github.io/filmography/lma/</guid>
      <description>My first project on episodic. The process is quite different than feature. You rely on being the most efficient and setting things up globally. One light rig to control as many shots as possible. I worked on episode 1 and 3. My sequences were for the most part heavy in effects (snow storm and sand storm).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spider-Man Into the Spider-Verse</title>
      <link>https://ouirich.github.io/filmography/spiderverse/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 22:50:30 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ouirich.github.io/filmography/spiderverse/</guid>
      <description>A very special project. I joined the show at the end for the last push. The amount of work done in compositing was tremendous, a lot was done in Nuke where we could be creative.
I worked on multiple sequences on lighting and shared some shots for the compositing task.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smallfoot</title>
      <link>https://ouirich.github.io/filmography/smallfoot/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Sep 2018 21:43:25 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ouirich.github.io/filmography/smallfoot/</guid>
      <description>First project with Katana. After one week of training that taught us the basics of Katana, we jumped into production.
Making the white characters readable on white snow was challenging. Scene optimization was a must for a show with crowd of hairy characters.
I worked on multiple sequences from lighting to compositing, 3D stereo included.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Peter Rabbit</title>
      <link>https://ouirich.github.io/filmography/peterrabbit/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 20:02:44 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ouirich.github.io/filmography/peterrabbit/</guid>
      <description>Most of the job was character lighting. First we had a blocking phase with colorchecker and mirror/gray ball matching. Shot lighting was adding lights and special treatment for the eyes.
The sequences taking place in the burrow were fully done in CG. Some compositing was done by the lighting team before handing off to the compositing team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The LEGO Ninjago Movie</title>
      <link>https://ouirich.github.io/filmography/ninjago/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2017 20:00:11 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ouirich.github.io/filmography/ninjago/</guid>
      <description>My first animated feature, I believe this is one of the experience where I learnt the most in my career. I worked on multiple sequences from lighting to compositing, 3D stereo included.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Assassin&#39;s Creed</title>
      <link>https://ouirich.github.io/filmography/assasinscreed/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2016 20:02:44 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ouirich.github.io/filmography/assasinscreed/</guid>
      <description>I worked on the Abstergo&amp;rsquo;s escape sequence. Look-development and lighting on set extension.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Star Trek Beyond</title>
      <link>https://ouirich.github.io/filmography/startrekbeyond/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2016 20:02:44 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ouirich.github.io/filmography/startrekbeyond/</guid>
      <description>Moving from small studios in Paris to one of the biggest studio in London was challenging. I learned what was expected from me on a feature film in a big studio. I also got used to adapt to new pipeline and tools quickly to be efficient.
Lighting of the Enterprise, swarm ship, turbo lift and torpedo (Planet excluded)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Warriors Gate</title>
      <link>https://ouirich.github.io/filmography/warriorsgate/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2016 21:04:19 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ouirich.github.io/filmography/warriorsgate/</guid>
      <description>First experience on a feature film. I worked on the exterior set extension.
  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
