<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>animation on Ouirich Bounthavy</title>
    <link>https://ouirich.github.io/categories/animation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in animation on Ouirich Bounthavy</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 10:15:24 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ouirich.github.io/categories/animation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>LEGO Pixar Bricktoons</title>
      <link>https://ouirich.github.io/filmography/legopixarbricktoons/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 10:15:24 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ouirich.github.io/filmography/legopixarbricktoons/</guid>
      <description>Those short films used characters from Pixar movies. The original movies were great for reference. I worked on light rigs, then moved to the key shots until final completion for different episodes. I split the shots assignment to my team.
The Incredibles The scene taking place at the end of day, we went for the dusk. We wanted to have some sunlight to skim the trees and the roofs. The yellow lights from the the house and the backyard provided us a safe environment for the kids, in contrast to the darkness when Syndrome shows up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leo</title>
      <link>https://ouirich.github.io/filmography/leo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 22:22:22 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ouirich.github.io/filmography/leo/</guid>
      <description>Coming back to Animal Logic after five years as a senior lighting artist. The studio developped their own lighting software for their USD pipeline. But thanks to my previous experience, it was fairly easy to pick it up. Mostly because the logic behind it, was still the same.
We don&amp;rsquo;t always work on the most exciting shots on a production. As I started, another artist left. So I ended up picking up their shots to complete them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sonic Prime</title>
      <link>https://ouirich.github.io/filmography/sonicprime/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 21:43:25 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ouirich.github.io/filmography/sonicprime/</guid>
      <description>Sonic Prime was the first show using Katana at Wildbrain. Most of the artists had no previous experience with this software. They had to be train and helped during production.
The lighting department had two teams, each one was composed of a lead, three seniors and eight artists. My role was to lead my team and achieve the creative lighting goals of the director for the episode.
Preparation I had to plan episode to achieve deliverables.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spidey and his Amazing Friends</title>
      <link>https://ouirich.github.io/filmography/spideyamagingfriends/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 21:43:25 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ouirich.github.io/filmography/spideyamagingfriends/</guid>
      <description>I worked on 6 shorts and 10 episodes of the first season. Each episode was 11 minutes long and usually had between 4 or 5 keyshots. Most of the time I was in charge of 2 or 3 that had effects. My role was to setup keyshots in lighting and compositing beforehand. I would then work with my team on the rest of the episode.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LEGO Marvel Avengers: Climate Conundrum</title>
      <link>https://ouirich.github.io/filmography/lma/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2020 14:34:15 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ouirich.github.io/filmography/lma/</guid>
      <description>My first project on episodic. The process is quite different than feature. You rely on being the most efficient and setting things up globally. One light rig to control as many shots as possible. I worked on episode 1 and 3. My sequences were for the most part heavy in effects (snow storm and sand storm).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Willoughbys</title>
      <link>https://ouirich.github.io/filmography/willoughbys/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 19:20:36 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ouirich.github.io/filmography/willoughbys/</guid>
      <description>Worked on multiple sequences setting up lighting mood and compositing template on master and keyshots.
I led one the sequence in the candy factory, the biggest sequence of the film over 80 shots. I worked on most of the keyshots. I provided feedback to artists based on notes from the production designer and supervisor, and supported them until final approval.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spider-Man Into the Spider-Verse</title>
      <link>https://ouirich.github.io/filmography/spiderverse/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 22:50:30 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ouirich.github.io/filmography/spiderverse/</guid>
      <description>A very special project. I joined the show at the end for the last push. The amount of work done in compositing was tremendous, a lot was done in Nuke where we could be creative.
I worked on multiple sequences on lighting and shared some shots for the compositing task.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smallfoot</title>
      <link>https://ouirich.github.io/filmography/smallfoot/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Sep 2018 21:43:25 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ouirich.github.io/filmography/smallfoot/</guid>
      <description>First project with Katana. After one week of training that taught us the basics of Katana, we jumped into production.
Making the white characters readable on white snow was challenging. Scene optimization was a must for a show with crowd of hairy characters.
I worked on multiple sequences from lighting to compositing, 3D stereo included.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The LEGO Ninjago Movie</title>
      <link>https://ouirich.github.io/filmography/ninjago/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2017 20:00:11 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ouirich.github.io/filmography/ninjago/</guid>
      <description>My first animated feature, I believe this is one of the experience where I learnt the most in my career. I worked on multiple sequences from lighting to compositing, 3D stereo included.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coldplay - Adventure of A Lifetime</title>
      <link>https://ouirich.github.io/filmography/coldplay/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Nov 2015 22:55:39 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ouirich.github.io/filmography/coldplay/</guid>
      <description>I started on the project by doing some lookdev work on different assets: vegetation and music instruments. I was in charge of lighting most of the shots in the jungle path sequence.
Mathematic was still a small studio, making a 5 minutes in full CG in less than 4 months was challenging. The set dressing has been made in a way to make the jungle dense. The biggest difficulty we had was making the light go through all that vegetation.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
