<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>animal-logic on Ouirich Bounthavy</title>
    <link>https://ouirich.github.io/tags/animal-logic/</link>
    <description>Recent content in animal-logic on Ouirich Bounthavy</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 22:22:22 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ouirich.github.io/tags/animal-logic/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Leo</title>
      <link>https://ouirich.github.io/filmography/leo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 22:22:22 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ouirich.github.io/filmography/leo/</guid>
      <description>Coming back to Animal Logic after five years as a senior lighting artist. The studio developped their own lighting software for their USD pipeline. But thanks to my previous experience, it was fairly easy to pick it up. Mostly because the logic behind it, was still the same.
We don&amp;rsquo;t always work on the most exciting shots on a production. As I started, another artist left. So I ended up picking up their shots to complete them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Peter Rabbit</title>
      <link>https://ouirich.github.io/filmography/peterrabbit/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 20:02:44 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ouirich.github.io/filmography/peterrabbit/</guid>
      <description>Most of the job was character lighting. First we had a blocking phase with colorchecker and mirror/gray ball matching. Shot lighting was adding lights and special treatment for the eyes.
The sequences taking place in the burrow were fully done in CG. Some compositing was done by the lighting team before handing off to the compositing team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The LEGO Ninjago Movie</title>
      <link>https://ouirich.github.io/filmography/ninjago/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2017 20:00:11 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ouirich.github.io/filmography/ninjago/</guid>
      <description>My first animated feature, I believe this is one of the experience where I learnt the most in my career. I worked on multiple sequences from lighting to compositing, 3D stereo included.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
