<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>episodic on Ouirich Bounthavy</title>
    <link>https://ouirich.github.io/categories/episodic/</link>
    <description>Recent content in episodic on Ouirich Bounthavy</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 10:15:24 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ouirich.github.io/categories/episodic/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>LEGO Pixar Bricktoons</title>
      <link>https://ouirich.github.io/filmography/legopixarbricktoons/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 10:15:24 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ouirich.github.io/filmography/legopixarbricktoons/</guid>
      <description>Those short films used characters from Pixar movies. The original movies were great for reference. I worked on light rigs, then moved to the key shots until final completion for different episodes. I split the shots assignment to my team.
The Incredibles The scene taking place at the end of day, we went for the dusk. We wanted to have some sunlight to skim the trees and the roofs. The yellow lights from the the house and the backyard provided us a safe environment for the kids, in contrast to the darkness when Syndrome shows up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sonic Prime</title>
      <link>https://ouirich.github.io/filmography/sonicprime/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 21:43:25 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ouirich.github.io/filmography/sonicprime/</guid>
      <description>Sonic Prime was the first show using Katana at Wildbrain. Most of the artists had no previous experience with this software. They had to be train and helped during production.
The lighting department had two teams, each one was composed of a lead, three seniors and eight artists. My role was to lead my team and achieve the creative lighting goals of the director for the episode.
Preparation I had to plan episode to achieve deliverables.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spidey and his Amazing Friends</title>
      <link>https://ouirich.github.io/filmography/spideyamagingfriends/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 21:43:25 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ouirich.github.io/filmography/spideyamagingfriends/</guid>
      <description>I worked on 6 shorts and 10 episodes of the first season. Each episode was 11 minutes long and usually had between 4 or 5 keyshots. Most of the time I was in charge of 2 or 3 that had effects. My role was to setup keyshots in lighting and compositing beforehand. I would then work with my team on the rest of the episode.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LEGO Marvel Avengers: Climate Conundrum</title>
      <link>https://ouirich.github.io/filmography/lma/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2020 14:34:15 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ouirich.github.io/filmography/lma/</guid>
      <description>My first project on episodic. The process is quite different than feature. You rely on being the most efficient and setting things up globally. One light rig to control as many shots as possible. I worked on episode 1 and 3. My sequences were for the most part heavy in effects (snow storm and sand storm).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
